Hello, do you know?
Wait
a minute?
Oh, uh,
hello, yes, hello. I brightened the destiny a little, but is
brighter better?
Or is it better than anything else? Wow, of
course. Can you hear my voice well?
The mic is still bad, so I bought a
dark one on purpose, but it
seems to be a bit off, so
oh, that's why I think I'll use a bright one. Hit it
today. Should I write the title like that from the beginning?
Hair loss,
Joseon, hair loss, k, deodorant. Hello,
Namildang. I'm also
thinking about whether to start talking about hair loss or wait a little longer. If you like it, I'll tell my
mother-in-law and move on.
This is similar to a
tree. I have to go see how it works. Do
you
know? The sound of the transfer is reversed. The installation is done. Pop. Is it coming from the mic? Should I change the home to an air phone? Ah, the one with the t-quarter mic doesn't fit? You said you can't do it. I'll pull it out again with my phone. So, please tell me if this is
better. Is this better? This is reversed. I think I need to use the router a bit.
Ah, but I'll get it quickly today in the morning. 4
i  Is
that better? Oh, sound waves. It's a sad reality. He always asks me to raise the microphone. Should I see if the arc is brighter? Oh, is it because the yin and yang are brighter? Oh, set the microphone like this. Otherwise, I'll borrow 2 pikes for a moment. Isn't that right? Yes,
there are so many.
Please wait a moment.
Oh, I
failed to borrow the bike. I
think that will do. It ca
n't be right.
Te.
Hello, is
this the sound of the mite? Is it small or big?
No, but I
bought the microphone anyway.
Together. 2
First of all, the reason is that it's worse than the foam earphone microphone. I'll just
leave it at
this level.
That car.
4 votes. If you vote
today, as I mentioned before, let's move on from the hair loss story.
Yes, let's laugh and
see.
Yes, let's
roll the face up to Pie 7. It's okay to do it like that. Do you
see this screen?
In that state, you can't see the chat.
But this is my first time doing this, so I don't know if you can see it well. It would be
nice.
r I made a ppt with my feet after a long time. Okay, if
I keep watching what you say here and there, the
explanation may be a little lacking.  We could go back and talk about that part again,
but since that's not the case, I'm a little worried. So, everyone, come and check your diet
through the monitor. While
talking about Formtec, if there's
anything
unclear or if you have any further questions, please
leave a comment after we're done. I'll go to the pantry.
Why isn't there a cafe?
Today, we'll talk about how chitosan can
treat hair loss, dandruff, and dermatitis. Until 2pm,
why do so many people who take it are
suffering from these problems? The
reason is that these problems may be due to a deficiency of vitamins B and D7.
Why are those possibilities so high? * People who say that height is not a risk factor?
Keto Cica may be especially applicable to them.
First, we'll talk about vitamin B2, riboflavin, and
vitamin P7B.
In this system, there are other vitamins like Vitra Utan MP7, but
there's a baby name for them.
And I think you've all heard of flavin and biotin B5.
If we say that hair loss is biotin, we'll take beer type 5.
First of all,
let's take a quick look at where these two nutrients are abundant and what they do in our bodies, even if it's not exactly intertwined.
Most fundamentally, these two nutrients are
abundant in the liver and kidneys, as well as in the intestines. In
addition,
egg yolks are the two foods that are overwhelmingly rich in these
two vitamins.
In addition, there are other foods, such as shepherd's purse and tea, but the amounts are
really close to the two foods mentioned above.
However, even so, if we were to choose a food from which we can obtain a certain amount, we
would choose meat. When I say meat here, I'm not talking about pork or riboflavin or tenderloin, but pork
belly and
such, of course, it includes other fish, shellfish,
mackerel, lobster, and other well-known foods. We're talking about all kinds of foods that are
rich in these foods, and so let's
start by looking at what riboflavin and vitamin D do.
Most fundamentally,
vitamin B2 riboflavin plays a very important role in energy metabolism in our bodies. If you
look here, there's something that seems complicated, right? You may have seen this in middle school
or
biology class at least once. It's called the Kraft cycle, or the
citric acid cycle.
It's the most fundamental and central circuit in our cellular metabolism. To put it simply,
it's the process of creating ATP from the carbohydrates, proteins, and fats we eat.
Here, ATP is like gasoline in a car.
Our body uses
date damage as fuel for
all bodily metabolism.
So, when you exert strength, when you blink, when you digest,
and in all tasks, you
can think of it as the most fundamental and central error that creates ATP. If you
look here, there are
various things written like DJ and so on. Those who have taken magnesium will
know these. Citrate citric acid gives
magnesium citrate, magnesium citrate, and malate malate. My appearance is new.  There are things like a10, 쨉심산, and
this succinic acid changes into 2-type ansan, and
there is this appearance where ad becomes ted h2, right?
Hey, the circled sailor part
etat is the active form of riboflavin, so it
looks like it's not doing it. Yes, pay d is riboflavin, and there are many other words.
Yes, that means riboflavin is
a part of this circuit that is fundamental to the eclipse cycle energy metabolism, which is very important in our body.
Riboflavin is a key axis in the eclipse cycle, so Loop Harvey
is a cooking energy company.
Next, it plays a very important role in antioxidant function.
Glutathione, which you've all probably heard of at least once, is
written as glutathione here.
Glutathione 2 is the most powerful and important antioxidant in our body. When
we think of antioxidants, we usually think of things like vitamin C or TAM,
but there are also polyphenols from plants.
Compared to those, the clutch
force is over a hundred times stronger. The gravity that acts as an antioxidant is hundreds of times stronger.
In our body, practically all antioxidant activities are
performed by humans, and the central substance is glutathione.
Glutathione is not immediately recognized once used. Our body
continuously recycles and uses this glutathione.
Before being used, glutathione is released, and later, after going to something else and fighting yellow dust,
sulfur oxides, and cheese, it changes to a tetra-oxidized state.
In order to recycle this acidic form of glutathione, the
action of a glow-touch reductase called the Blue Touch original guy, Touch Heat Duct Ace, is required.
And for the action of this reductase, as I said earlier, riboflavin and vitamin B2 are
absolutely necessary.
Therefore, our two always look at the four bottles, and the most powerful detective Maki's
second base touch-on plays a very important role.
In addition, global coffee time beat
riboflavin is a
very important new product, such as matte lation, of course.  Other
energies play an important role in many places in our body.
But the most important part we need to pay attention to here
is this part called the law.
2 Here, something is complicatedly set up like this. This
is the process by which our body uses beta-4 fatty acids as energy. If you
look here, there are numbers called Betty's CD, which is too much.
These chain pet sc dill and bang 3 fatty acids, if you think of them in Korean, are
all the forms of fat that we usually eat. They go through all the processes from the beginning to the end and
change into this shape at the bottom. As I mentioned earlier, the
kraph cycle is the
basis of all cellular metabolism, and this process shows the ratio.
So in the middle, this blue-green fatty acid is at the end of the stone. The rest is in the middle of the process. You
can see page 2, for example, on page 2. As I mentioned earlier, vitamin B and
vitamin B2 riboflavin are essential for fatty acid metabolism. They are
always essential for beta-4 fatty acids.
So, the
more fat we eat, and the more we consume and burn that fat as energy, the more this becomes.
Riboflavin FAD
means that the need for beets increases next.
In other words, it's the same as saying that a high-fat keto 3-4 diet
significantly increases terrorism because we use fat as an energy source instead of fighting a battle. It's like
[ __ ], so let's
put aside the club talk I just had and look at what biotin does
again. I
'll come back later. Ah, bye-bye
25t India. Like flying, it's essential for our body's energy metabolism. It
's used in many very difficult things, and among them, it's a
cofactor called carboxy-2-carboxyl ace, which is an enzyme that acts as a 2-carboxyl ace. The
element called 2-carboxy is essential for shooting. You can think of it as essential for shooting. In
addition, it's used in various military activities such as regulating the cell cycle of trees.
Since it's not carboxy-2, let's focus on it and recover and look at what's in it.
First, let's take a look at the sleep. That's Lacetti 1 nose cup 7.
We said earlier that the district SD cycle was like that.  This is the Krebs cycle I mentioned, and
the citric acid cycle
uses the metabolites produced here,
and the enzyme ACC is acetyl 552-acetyl buckyrialdehyde, which is an
abbreviated form.
This is used to create things like fatty acids in the intestines.
But this is something you can drink to some extent, and it's
really important for our bodies. It's really important for keto people who can't do it.
Among the tris, this part is the part that you have to do. The
shape of the character shows where the element called pyrocarboxy is used. If you
look at it like this, the pyrocarboxyrum element is this. If you look here, it
's called Pyro Beck Pearl Buck Slice in English.
This is the citric acid cycle that I mentioned, and it plays a
very important role.
So, if you give it a try, the role that beauty takes is that if beauty doesn't work, this professor
won't work, so biotin is very important. This
applies to everyone, not just people who are keto, but why is
it especially important for keto people? It has to look like this.  This is
because the produced foreign substances, which are in the form of carboxyl group, later rise up and go through this process to create glucose again, called glyconeogenesis, which is a malignant process that you may have heard of at least once.
What is gluconeogenesis? If you are a
phytosician, you may have heard of it at least once. In our body, there are cells that absolutely need glucose,
such as red
blood cells. Even if we have completely adapted to ketosis,
there are cells that absolutely need glucose. If we hear that news, our glucose intake
will inevitably decrease naturally. Then, when we
look at the
glucose that they need, the body makes it directly from other materials, mainly amino acids, other proteins, and fats, rather than this single glucose.
Therefore, people on a ketogenic diet
inevitably have a higher demand for gluconeogenesis.  Biosynthesis requires this.
Let's go to Busan Carboxy Lahee. It's essential because it's used.
As glucose de novo synthesis increases, the 2.2g increase in biotin
requirement increases.
Ah,
and in addition, there are
three amino acids called B-seed, isoleucine, 1-sin, and allin. You
can live with odd-chain fatty acids.
There's something complicated here, but if I summarize it simply, it's like this.
B-seed refers to three amino acids.
In Korean, we call them Eunji 3 amino acids. These are usually the
proteins. To
put it simply, they are the ones in the protein powder that people who do hell's eat. In order for
these three amino acids to enter our bodies and be metabolized, this matt
chronico aunt cloned them and put them in the nose cup. Maybe because
both of these are set up as carboxyl.
These enzymes are essential for metabolizing them. The
main action of these enzymes is to
convert 2pc of work into energy in the body.  It can create cholesterol and then
create keto.
The amino acid called new keto is converted into two-tone after being metabolized.
So, the more PCA we eat, the more
our biotin needs increase.
This is because of the three reasons I mentioned earlier: foods rich in riboflavin, such as the
liver, internal organs, egg yolks, and meat, as you
mentioned. When you eat meat, the amount of light is revealed in this way. So, if you
only eat meat,
you will be in a hurry to meet the biotin needed for PC metabolism. If you only
eat meat, you
may not be able to completely meet the biotin needs in other places.
Next, let's move on for a moment and look at
chain fatty acids. Professor, chain fatty
acids are structural molecules with a carbon chain that is connected.
Among them, most are even-numbered, but there are some that are odd-numbered. They are
mainly found in dairy products.
In the case of chain fatty acids, when Dajeong is metabolized, only
one is used, so only one is left.  There are cases where
they can't metabolize properly, so they combine all the cholesterol we eat
and put it into a cup company, and through the enzymes we need,
we lose the succinate of the Cripps terror and make this
* 9 minutes. Now, this is again clicked and goes in and turns into energy. Hops, Gin, and
Sulfur fatty acids are combined into energy. To make it into energy, we need another duty me. Let's
summarize what we've talked about so far. The
bomb is a person, but Q explodes, so continue.
Those of you watching this broadcast right now, don't forget. What kind of
diet is it? It's a diet that converts carbohydrates into fat as an energy source by eating less carbohydrates and more fat.
4 If you follow this book's method, the
support for gluconeogenesis increases, and the intake of CA increases.
Since you eat a lot of fat, the intake of fatty acids is also revealed.
In particular, dairy products such as butter and other cheeses are eaten a lot.
That's why these people's intake is high.  And to metabolize all of this, we
need to increase the amount of fat. This means that our body's memory team needs will
increase by following the Keto monk's diet.
And in addition, as the fat intake itself increases and the work of breaking down that fat
begins, the needs for the fat 3, beta 4, and riboflavin that I mentioned earlier will
inevitably increase as well. To
summarize, because we haven't been able to do it, by following the Keto diet so far, our team
needs will increase and the
need for riboflavin will increase.
Ah, the needs have increased like this, but our body is
n't providing enough of the 5 guns.
So when a deficiency occurs,
there are various things that happened using the layers.
And there's this flop in de and this beauty, and these two overlap, and that's
Iru Seongki 90.
Seborrheic dermatitis, as you can see in the picture earlier, refers to the red rash that mainly appears on the face,
especially around the nose, mouth, and eyebrows, and
each area appears together.
And this is only on the face.  It's not that it's there, but it's solved with scalp um, but
belief is created in the head, and
552 Ok-hee's keratin occurs, and these things are
all collectively called, and now these are connected and hair loss occurs, for
example, deficiency is a symptom of
seborrheic dermatitis, so it's called first-line 2p 0
dandruff hair loss and values ​​2 2 0 0 3 can be caused by deficiency.
And one more thing to note is that there is a spiritual decline, and
if you feel it, if you have a deficiency, your academic ability will drop.
This means that the Candida bacteria and the diet become vulnerable.
For example, when we talk about sterilized home cooking, we usually think of 10 or so, and
many of us think of things that are over-cooked,
but
seborrheic dermatitis and Chilseok scalp um
are also thought to be caused by a specific wise person called Ala 3 Jia over-proliferating in our skin, and it's a machine that pops up. But because
we have those special suspects, our immunity is lacking and the
content is low, so those seafood bacteria over-proliferate in our skin.  Proliferation
can contribute to dermatitis and the presence of the first ballot box.
Then, let's review the factors that increase the possibility of this top.
Why? There are many, but the
most common problem is that it applies to all nutrients. If there is a
respiratory problem or poor absorption, such as a
disability like Crohn's disease or
severe sugar leakage, even if the child eats a lot of good food, the
child will not grow and will not absorb it well.
When there is a problem like this, and until recently, when following the Arte low-carb koji diet, the
burden increases and the club's required amount increases, and what is gluconeogenesis?
C, Hall,
flower, manual installation, room items, etc. In addition, riboflavin can be caused by
overexertion or excessive tanning. Flaminin is vulnerable to light.
If it is exposed to excessive light, it can cause inflammation. Excessive tanning,
poor observation of food, spreading food in the sun,
exposing food to too much light in the eyes, or making the food
too small. These are all things that can cause inflammation. No, riboflavin
can be cooked and made into kibi.  And in the
case of rooting, egg whites are the largest.
Egg whites contain a protein called biotin, which binds to powerful environmental factors, such as BD. The
effect is stronger when Atkins or egg whites are not leaked.
So, if you eat egg whites without cooking them often, eat a lot of raw eggs, or
pass them over with Arc Click,
there are people who eat raw eggs too often or just eat egg whites.
In such cases, biotin deficiency can occur in our bodies
because of bodybuilding. Others can be due to liver disease or genetic factors.
In fact, the other problems are
not that big of a problem because
there are more people who don't exercise much. I think it's
mostly sunlight deficiency and I
can't do it. In the case of the new method, it's not known what happens during the distribution process, so it
's definitely a possibility, but there aren't many people who drink alcohol that often while eating 2C Cassie.
There are
a lot of people who don't eat eggs at all, not egg whites.
There are many people who
say they can't be allergic, but
there are also many who don't eat eggs at all.  I'm not doing it, and
epilepsy is not common, so is it
really true that we are increasing the possibility? What is the real problem?
What is the biggest problem in reality? This is it.
I made this presentation yesterday, but
somehow it was taken at 7:19 PM. Sojin gave it to me. I'll
just take a picture of it as it is in the Keto profit section of today's photo cafe. If you
look at it as it is, I said earlier that Lee Du-young is plentiful. The
liver, kidneys, and large intestine are the
most abundant. The yolk is the most abundant here, and I said that it is abundant in ramen.
This means that today's Kyoto-style
food is offered by people who take pictures and upload them because they
think it is
okay, and it is nicely presented and suitable for people to see. They
eat well through Hongseong and take pictures and upload them.
Despite this, if you look at the things at that time, the premier course is
5 cat bread and butter
elode and here, there are two egg yolks,
but other than that, there is salad and plata cheese. This station is one
joint, 5
team noodles.  The person said that he has been eating brown rice, but there is
almost no shaking.
This kind of
inside is about 5 minutes. It is said that he used a tree and most of the meat itself is
less than 150g to 200g. There are
almost no yolks or eggs, and there are
no internal organs. If you
look here, you can see sweet potatoes and
pumpkins, so only butter is like this. As I mentioned earlier, if fat intake increases, it is
inevitable that a lot of riboflavin is needed, but there is
not a single one that contains
riboflavin. Yes, I understand that people who eat this much eat a lot of fat and reduce carbohydrates, but beyond that, what are the nutrients that our body actually needs?
By doing the ketogenic diet, we
worry about what nutrients our body may need more of every time we eat a regular diet. Because of this
absence of worries, we eat like this.
Yes, we eat like this.
And pine nuts. Let's talk directly about eating like this. If we eat like this, our children are
bound to suffer from hair loss. Like this, at the age of 10.  Hair loss,
growth, and support, and the quality of the product I mentioned earlier, no, this is a
plugin and but, you can't help but suffer from deficiency symptoms together.
Here,
and if you
look at it once, if you search for
50,
today is April 2nd, and until February 23rd, Mama, this
is the reality where articles related to hair loss are pouring out.
Hehe, whether I did something wrong with the feeder or not, I
got caught up in the soup.
How should I paint? The
solution to hair loss and support. The
most important thing is to
eat the intestines and yolk when you eat it. It's
important to get enough flavins, excluding the team.
So, I'm talking about this store and yolk intake. You can eat 250g of liver 4 times a week and
4 yolks every day.
Sprinkle them on your meals like this.
We're not just talking about healthy people without any problems, but
about people who already have hair loss.
Hair loss is a healthy thing.  If you do, and you're currently healthy and have no cancer problems and are
following the keto diet, you might not need to eat this much.
But if you're going
through the same issues I've been having, I
recommend eating at least 250g of liver a week. 250g a week is
only about 30g of curry. Kindly, no. You
can use 3 egg yolks a day. And
besides, our bodies also have a lot of beets.
Besides that, other minerals can cause vitamin D deficiency.
Here, we're talking about real food. It can be produced when we eat, or
seafood.
By eating more than 500g of these a day, you
can prevent most deficiencies.
By replacing 500g of meat with this,
I explained this last time.
And by eating like this, all of our
hair is made of collagen. Most of it is made of collagen.
In Clarke, we consume collagen directly, along with other amino acids and other
proteins.  It means that it is made with that protein. So, it
is very important to eat enough protein in this way.
However, I have followed all these things for
several weeks, and even for several months, but the mulkala continues to fall out and it does
not seem to be helping.
In that case, we can consider taking this supplement.
In the case of riboflavin, you
can try taking 500mg of 400mg every day. In the case of Tim, you can try taking more than 5,000, and up
to 5,000 in the body.
If this does not work with the 8 program, then now, based on the judgment of the functional medicine bottle, we can conduct organic tests
such as a flat test to see what our body is really experiencing. We can determine whether
consuming enough food in this way
will solve the problem.
Oh, and we talked about bread together, but
this is something that the child should write down after hearing what was said in front, but if you
look here, the teacher, the photo communication biosynthesis 2
Leez has increased and now biotin blood.  I went to Sanglim, and
because of this, we were told that we would suffer from hair loss even on the tour we were going to do, so I tried to eat more carbohydrates. There's
no specific nutrient in these carbohydrates, and that nutrient doesn't
solve the nutrient deficiency. It's not like carbohydrates solve hair loss.
It's literally purely a matter of how our body's
biosynthesis site is reduced, and this is the most fundamental and biggest factor.
Because the lead for gluconeogenesis is reduced,
our body no longer needs to use biotin here, so we
can always save this much.
And since we eat more carbohydrates, fat intake will also decrease, and we'll eat
less meat. Because of these things, people who
don't eat really good food anyway and sprinkle things like salad on their diet for 5 days can
eat rice instead. Instead, they
can see the effects of biotin and the necessary plug-in. It's
not a fundamental solution. And in addition, as insulin
works more strongly, insulin converts
thyroid hormones well, so it's virtual.
Keeper can convert T3 better, like
Beauty Story.  In this case, riboflavin 2
is converted from flavin to FAD, so I
could touch on that part, but I wanted to say that it is not a fundamental solution.
Ah, so yes, I
will try to explain it this far.
I know,
right now, 08:40 5
Kao, I understand this year.
Well, I
tried to explain it in a reflective way, but I'm not sure if I conveyed it well. I'm planning
to use it at a company dinner, but it
took longer than I thought. English 5
Anyway, that 4 is
good. So, if you do the tour extremely wrong, your
health can deteriorate. There are other things to throw out besides this.
This is what I briefly
went over for the arc earlier.
And there are also things that come from deficiency, right?
Yes, the inside of the mouth is sore, the lips are swollen, and the cornea is swollen. Is it wiping? There are
quite a few people who have eye-related problems or eye inflammation. Even if you
vomit and eat enough 8 times, it
doesn't improve anemia. Riboflavin is necessary for iron.
In addition, pot, mobile, it's natural for fingernails and toenails to become weak, and
there are people who have nervous problems and a bad mood.  You
might think that people who don't eat carbohydrates just sit around and chat, but there are things like this, and in fact, biotin and
protein are not like that, so if you eat
carbs, it
can actually cause more problems. I've said this many times before, but the
definition of "what is it?" is very loose. I've
always said that eating only canola and salads on top of canola is a
keto diet. Can we be healthy if we eat like that?
Well, if you look at it that way, it
doesn't mean that everything will automatically get better just because you cut down on ginseng.
Later, I'll organize and edit the parts that I stumbled over in the middle of my speech and
come back to you. If you
mix flowers or get wet from the moment you hear it or don't understand well, I'll upload a
video that I'll edit and upload later.
I think you can just pick it up. There are
a lot of things to
do. 4.
People on a regular diet eat egg yolks, but they think that the yolks contain fat and cholesterol, which are
bad for the body, so they don't eat the white yolks. It's
very dangerous. Protein  Our bodies
need a lot of different nutrients to function properly. Night 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 9 ...
It's okay to eat only one or two things that suit you mentally. 5. I
hope you eat a little bit of basic food while going through the store. Also, if you
eat various foods at other stores in between,
there are more nutrients in the auction houses of those stores.
5. In the case of kidneys, there is a lot of selenium, and since it is a system,
those who are deficient can eat those by eating kidneys.
There are also many of these in the bone marrow, and the brain is also in the body,
so people with a lot of work to do are made of things like stabs.
But in the case of meat, there is
no need to eat them in turns. However,
there are some foods that should not be eaten as a staple food.
Pork, or if I eat it every day,
it is equivalent to pork or equivalent to pork. I don't think it is good because it is not very natural and
has too much unsaturated fat. If you are
going to eat mainly balloons and mountain climbing, I think it is good.
I have a lot of good health, but I think you used an exaggerated word.
Rather than making fish that is too oily, if you are going to eat a lot of fish, it is better to
use a production that does not have a lot of names. It means adding animal products from other places and making bread
from land animals.  I
think it would be good to do
it. It doesn't matter if you trade beef or grains or something like that. Also, when you don't consume internal organs, your hair will fall out and it's like a special pardon. Oh, this is really the keto period. I've been like that since day 4, and
Mr. Yang said that keto doesn't mean anything because you eat a lot of meat. There was a reason for that.
So, it's important to eat a lot of reviews. It's
not something else. I mean, as I said earlier, the keto diet is literally the
keto period where you eat patented Nola No 2 tricky and salad.
Our body will be able to hitoshi, so we
can use it very happily. If
we eat like that, but if we can't get our bodies out of the ketosis state, we
can do that, but in our spring,
that process isn't the goal. We want better health, better
vitality, 0 habits, tone, and things like that. Or maybe it's the
treatment of other diseases, improvement of symptoms, or a
healthy opportunity. I don't know, but there's no other cancer. The purpose is to
process the tone of the body among the stars.
If we want to do that without a purpose, what we need to do is not to make the cylinders circulate in the blood, but to
return to the diet that humans were originally designed to eat, as a hobby.
As I told you, we eat a lot of animal products and supplement the rest with whatever we
want,
whether it's red beans or the most basic thing is to eat a lot of meat.
That's because that
's the diet that's suitable for us. As
you can see, just listen to the
land, what's the beet? Eat soup, intestines, or
raw fruits.
If you want to see the effects in stages, you can buy supplements and take them.
To do this, should the egg white pattern person do it all? In
my case,
[music] I
don't eat egg whites. When you
cook them, the effects are greatly reduced, so it's
not that bad. In addition, there
are many reasons for egg allergies. When you
see people at Musk Cafe, some
people think that Asians have a lot of allergies to sweets, but it's
not just Asians; it's just people who have a lot of allergies.
At the Anyang event, that's because I ate all the bad foods I ate as a child, and I ate egg whites.
Since we eat together and do this, I don't think there's any possibility of thinking about it,
but anyway, egg whites
contain things that can cause allergies or other negative effects in the spring,
so it's difficult to eat, is
n't it? If I find it really hard to eat protein, it's
really hard to eat the number in grams when I convert my body weight to pounds of protein I need per day. I'm
not getting enough.
In that case, I shouldn't leave out egg whites, but
eating protein is not easy. It's hard to get fat from a good course.
If you ride a bike, you'll only get the yolk, so you'll take the yolk because it means excluding the white. There are cigarettes in the yolk. I
think this will be a little different for everyone. Those who can't eat a lot of protein anyway, you should
n't throw it away. It's so precious.
The egg white has protein,
but now, up to 1, egg whites have almost all the protein and
almost no other nutrients.
90% of the nutritionists in eggs are in the yolk. There are
so many articles saying it's okay to eat vegetable oil and not Toki Towers.  I was
wondering what this was.
So, it
seems like there are so many people who have become gluttons. I
don't know how or why it happens, but it's
just like Khan. It's just a means to an end.
What we really want is to gain stars through good eating habits.
Losing weight means losing weight, improving athletic ability means improving stamina, and
losing Brim Po. That's how Bennett Lee's goal
should be.
Once the goal itself becomes yours, you're now just chasing after it. No matter
how good other people say nutrients, supplements, or food are, if
you really don't like them, you shouldn't eat them.
For example, the 8-grain eating habits, healthy eating habits, and the name board are all just means at the end of the app.
You all know that I ate 400g of it instead of four, but my stomach hurt for half a day and I
didn't eat anything. I
also had a spoonful of coconut oil during the spoonful. Later, I was sick.
I thought I was breaking down fat and protein incorrectly, but I
ate more than 500g.  I can't do it. Is it because I'm born with a deficiency in fat and protein?
Hair loss, low body weight, and even below the age of 10, is it because I'm born with a deficiency in protein? It's
really rare,
but it's possible that a genetic mutation suddenly occurs and I can't do anything. Is that not possible? No, it's not. But
it's generally very rare. In such cases, the first thing that comes to mind is a
problem with the double chin. If your thyroid function is not good,
then digestion is not proper. And now, the subcutaneous
phase may not be secreted well.
However, if you eat a little too much, it looks bad. Hey, Lee Sang-
gon, it's important to eat enough gum. It's important to eat 10g of salt every day. It's
important to have high cholesterol and fat in a form that can be well absorbed.
Right now, if your body can't break down and digest food,
then I need to fix my current body condition based on those ingredients and nutrients, but
that's not working well. As I mentioned earlier, there's
malabsorption, a digestive problem, or something like that.  If you have it, all the nutrients
won't be absorbed well. It's
really important because it's the basis of all our health, so it's
very important. It's something you need to think about seriously right now. If it
doesn't work right away, I recommend taking digestive enzyme supplements. It would be
good to get tested at a hospital to see if your acidity is low.
Depending on the results, you can
adjust the amount of enzymes you take. For now, I recommend getting your thyroid checked and reducing your salt intake by at least 10g.
And when eating fat, it
's better to eat solid fat, rather than liquid fat. If fat is liquid, it moves too quickly
to the address, so it keeps getting taken away, and
the fat that's created can cause this feta.
So, if you
look at the fat attached to meat, it's not
yet a lump of fat, so eat it raw or whatever.
It's better to eat it raw.
I would like you to attend because it is better.
I am a man who takes biotin and vitamin B complex supplements while doing po color.
So what can't I do? But now, it is always better to
eat real food rather than supplements.
The form is like that, and the mouth is better, and the absorption rate is lowered, and those
strict supplements are not that good. But now,
if I do
n't need others and I don't
know, I can't eat it. I eat meat,
intestines, egg yolks, and all of that, I tell
you to eat it as much as you can.  There are people who don't see results even after eating. I
'm eating really well right now, but in the past, the deficiency was
so severe that no matter how much I put it in food, the deficiency couldn't be diagnosed.
Yes, it's not rare, but it's rarer than you think.
In cases like Gaebyeokbeon Baekho, high-dose supplements are necessary. It doesn't end with just Vitamin B Complex.
Murphy type complex is the basic intake, and the measurement value,
the second part, beet, etc., which is the origin of
this team, need to be taken separately in high doses.
Where do you buy the opening? Oh, and I made a 2-pack that I call the
VSI Place Korea and Seoul Chapter Guy Processing Street.
[Music] You can
give it to each other on the blog, or send me a muffler, a private comment,
or something like that via Instagram DM. If you
have any questions, I'll attach a picture. It's set
to be public for 6 people. Later,
4 people will
be a little known to the public, and it
seems like there will be an end,
so I made it public for the light function.
And the chin is difficult.  I saw it at Hwang Seong-tae's, but other than that,
if you do this or just leave a comment, I'll send you a link in a private comment.
Ren is
probably a
cow or sheep that grazes on pasture, and I think it's hard to find in our country. If you do
n't
regret it, they sell it at the market. There are people who work on the cow's head, so the price is really cheap. As for the hand, it's because it's so regrettable that I played around.
Ah, I don't know. It's
better to share it than not to eat it.
But,
ah, I don't know.
2. I don't know exactly what it means. Is it good to
eat it consistently even though it's not that, or is
it worse? But I think there's a blood pressure expectation wall when I think about it, so I
think it's the cleanest in Hanwoo rather than other regions, but
since the breeding environment is so poor, I
don't think it's a big deal. I spent 500 won, but when I bought it, they
said it was usually around 1,000 won. It's a livestock market in Majang-dong,
but if you don't pick on it, you
can't do it
in one.  500 won, 1000 won, like this,
oh, oh, that's right, I usually eat that large intestine these days, but I
also buy the whole fish and eat it.
Since they don't throw away the intestines that are thrown away at places like sushi restaurants or Taesan water specialty stores, I
get them and grill them together and
that's it. Or, I eat whole fish like smelt and consume it that way.
Since I eat salvation almost every day, if you
look at videos of people in the past who were negative, they often drew out goat, red spirit, and other
things to eat. Doesn't this have the same effect as boiling when heated? There are
n't many eggs. So, it's true that some people ate it by pulling it like this,
but if it were just the number inside, there are more people who didn't boil it. But in
Mongolia, it's especially
bitter, so they ate it because there's that half, and it's like hacking, and it tastes like a mixture of various things. Those people basically don't eat other foods that can finish the intestines, so there's almost no chance of the amount being destroyed, so
I think that's where the biggest damage is. Modern people are skinny married and don't eat whole
grains or anything.  It's awesome.
And if you
look at one more thing, these ancient people are the ones who are the ones who are the ones we see boiling and eating now. There are
no Park No-soos, and there's nothing we can be excited about because they're perfectly
healthy. Because in the case of tribes that were actually really healthy or not, in the
case of tribes that were clearly examined, most of them did
n't preach about it, didn't boil it, and consumed it right away. The
Swiss did it, the Masai did it,
so
this isn't it, but it's a little bit like that. There are also controversial parts because of this.
People who pasteurize and drink milk are like that. In the case of the explanation, if you were to say that people in the body and the people at the
watchtower were
all bad, wouldn't those people remember it?
That's not entirely wrong. That kind of logic itself,
but what we can broaden is
what happens when pasteurization enters our bodies. It's
terrible. The more we
know, the more we dig into it, the more we see, and the more we see, the more we realize that it's really painful.
So, if you think about it, there were people in the past who said that if you put it on your face, it would
get rid of wrinkles.  It
might not be a good thing, but it's true.
Behind the home page, there was only a dog, and there was no heart mountain. It was easy to get
a point, and the intestines of the
sheep settled down and used it. Teach me, and it was safe. The fat with three sides is also good for dumplings. Ah, this is really like a candle. Tips like this are
definitely something to remember and at least use. The
sheep store is really good. The amount applied here is like Madeleine flour.
These
young animals' liver is milder with a broth. In the
case of impressions, the taste is too strong, so many
people can't eat it well. Those who really like the taste of liver will like it better, but most people who don't.
Since there aren't many people who have eaten it well since childhood,
so lamb liver and things like this are
generally easier and more convenient to eat. Oh, that's why I
like it. I
changed it to a loud restaurant. My brain function was good.
Oh, so my probe has improved a lot. As the
music
reversed, like Cree said, my IQ went up by 32. I don't know more about this,
but Sanford is getting better. But I have that. So, if I'm just being honest, I
think this could be better.  I think I could live better,
but I'm going to go to the Dal-kal industry, and I'm going to
focus and
think clearly because I'm going after the after-life. I think Maca could be better, but I think it
could be better than this. I keep thinking about it,
so I'm studying obsessively, and
that's why I'm doing it. It's pretty good,
or the best right now, and I don't usually think about it. I
think it could get better, so I'll think a lot about how I can get better. If I could
become a genius after 4 years, it would be good once more. The
lower part was more than I thought. The
red part is more than the mocha
vaccine layer. There are many eggs that are extracted from me, so there are many white allergies and side effects. The
egg white is not the only problem. It's filled with heavy metals and things
like aluminum. Aluminum is a representative example, and it's
not a cycle in the death of the vaccine. So if we don't put in heavy metals, the vaccine won't be
approved by our body, so it causes problems. We have to hit
that problem and build immunity. If we want to cause that problem, we
have to put in a 110-degree ionizer.
So, people who have 110 degrees are okay with eating heavy metals again.  It's okay, those heavy metals, etc.,
don't poke each other, blood vessels directly, g pad, it's okay to talk about it, but I
like receiving sexy, so I think it's okay
to include body weight, so did you nod your head?
No, it's the 307 scent.
Calculate the amount of protein in 307 meat separately and use that amount of protein
when you change the fund for that weight.
In general, most songs are just like that. If you talk at a general level, usually
5, if you're hungry, roughly drink it.
About 20% is protein. Generally,
if Gauguin is 500g, protein is about 100g. If you think about it, it's
right. If there's a lot of fat around that area, the
comeback cherry will decrease, and if it's bread and meat without children, some things will increase a little bit, and things
like that.
Depending on the fish or things like that, it will do little by little.
If you try to choose a lot of tones, you'll end up with something.
Okay, if you listen, is the restaurant
okay? The fact that we can eat this much food is because this is the 21st century. We live in Korea in 2020, so that's g. Even in the 21st century, if you go to a poor African village right now, they eat the same thing they eat every day. Can't you help it?  When you think about it logically, other animals are different, so
other animals, not humans, think about things like, "What do I want to eat today? I should eat that. What do I
look at today?
What should I write down? Oh, I ate too much of that jar yesterday, so I
should eat a lot of mugwort. I know that if I eat a lot of mugwort, I'll have a latent allergy." We
don't think like that.
It's important to consume a variety of foods that provide the nutrients our bodies need. And it's important to consume all the nutrients. We need to
eat a variety of foods. Ah,
this isn't a set rule. Especially,
meat is a food that rarely causes allergies. It's not like I have an allergy during the rainy season. What should I do? It's not like I have no shame in the National Assembly and there are no sm5 k5 women and so on. This is a food that practically doesn't have a tooth. It's not
like I'm tall and I don't have a tooth. ...  It's
different, but in the case of chickens, especially now that they're raised in factory farms, they're really surprised and
don't tilt their heads, but they're really tall in the room,
and there's a
lot of controversy about omega books, and the main cause is soybeans, corn, and
soybeans, and soybeans can be used in businesses, so it's not good, but
they're really good because they're grown repeatedly on pasture.
9 New meat is especially high in phytan kate, and
of course, when you eat grass, of course, these days, people love the malicious vitamin K3,
and they say that the content of charcoal is high,
but there's no
photo error. In the case of our river, especially when you burn it, there's a lot of charcoal,
almost phytan k2 blue li, so if you eat it naturally, if
your roots are destroyed, there's no food. There's
no turnkey exploration compared to all other foods, and besides that, look at that, invitation
measures,
but now, quality is important.
How did the water not work? How did they grow it? It's better than
evil, but we're better and
things like that, or there
are almost no names for shooting, so anyway, it's all good.
Hello, at the Oriental Medicine Clinic, they say red ginseng is good.  What do you think about trying elixir? I do
n't know much about Noh Kyung. I wonder if
it's because I'm sick. Yes, we
don't eat deer antler every day to take care of our health. If
we have a problem, we go to a Korean medicine clinic and a doctor diagnoses us
and
makes herbal medicine with deer antler. I
don't really want to have a problem with taking it as medicine under the judgment of an experienced doctor with red ginseng. I don't have that kind of feeling.
I think it's unnecessary for general health management. How do people eat red ginseng? People who eat it because of the phone are
very bad for the room. It's basically a summary of reading.
Of course, most of the first things that everyone does are like that. It's good.
Anyway, it's good. I do it like this and now I eat it, but
Pony is originally a 9-minute anti-aging drug,
so I don't think it's good to eat fried ginseng or red ginseng every day.
Hey, let's move on.  You can do it,
right? I don't think I've accumulated any stress. It's a bit vague.
Tess is also stressed.
Oh, I tried the base for the first time recently and it was so delicious.
Harmony. I heard it's sold as a product, but can I eat it as a product other than the living quarters? I
don't know. What did you say earlier? The
seasoning is a little bit, and I don't think that really matters, but I wonder how the cooking process is.
If you say it's made without kimchi, it's usually wrapped low in aluminum foil and seasoned with
various ingredients.
The cooking process is a bit like that,
but one thing is certain. It's better than eating it. It's
obvious.
It's not easy for wild babies to eat the base. It's a bit difficult to buy, and it's also a bit difficult to get.
So you can eat it without knowing it.
However, the reason you don't buy it is because it's already cooked and distributed.
Then, it doesn't produce this kind of oily substance. My wife's
body is full of blood. Taboo saturated fatty acids, omega-3s, and
these guys use it. The probability of Tess is very high.
It's okay to make it right away in a special lecture, but it's good.
If you earn money and pull out the headache,
one of them will die.  The exchange rate is very high and
the process is a bit difficult, so I trade. I
hope that if it can mean doing it, I will definitely think about it for a period of time. I saw the Demon World Hall originally. They
say it's the pore of the sea that is the
best. I'm saving up. I'm going to do it. I'm going to stab one stone without a pig. The ingredients are pork liver. It passed through 40 and now it hurts. And 5% of Sohu-eun will welcome the bus. The clincher smart 0.1% octagonal laurel licorice root stem is said to be boiled. Yes,
what do you think? Ah, the first chuck
monosodium glutamate 0.1%. Those who are sensitive to this won't be able to eat it, but
those who aren't will. I have an
allergic reaction like this. My heart pounds and
this kind of thing.
Seocho, like this.
Ah, I always say that
eating noodles is a million times better than not eating them.
Eat it anyway.
First, eat it. You can see how you can raise the quality of what you eat to a higher level.
Especially, think about whether you can eat better things.
After eating, do it.  Even before eating, you can tell that there
are a lot of additives in it. It seems like there are a lot of them. It's
because of the water,
but I've seen that additives are bad,
but
uh, looking at it a little more broadly, if I don't eat at the store because of the additives,
that's even worse. Of course, it depends on what and how much the additives are, but I
hope you think about it in a holistic way like this.
The picture is a southern-facing chibang newspaper. It's a lump of Chiba. Ah, I
should have told you about that. I
spoke to the CEO of G a while ago. It's a little bit, but when you
hand it over to the company, it's
not 2,000 won, but it's a
few hundred won. They're handing it over in bulk at a higher price than the initial price. They're handing it over in boxes at a time.
That's how they've been handing it over, but when I started asking questions,
I steadily became an island person, and I
was riding on the interest rate as a service, but
recently,
there are people who buy only four seasonings and order two fats.
From the company's perspective, that upgrade is a good thing.
First of all,
there are the reward costs and labor costs, right?
After receiving that, we package it, freeze it, finance it, and send it out. The
icebox used for packaging it costs
close to 1,000 won, but in fact, they
only send it in multiple rooms, and
there are also cases where this doesn't fit. Originally, the room itself costs 2,000 won per kilogram of fat, and if you
pass it on to 233 dimensions,
that amount will be enough. It won't be enough for the party.
[Music]
Many couples
still order that fat, but it wasn't originally 2,000 won, and we saw a few hundred won for the second time.
And the 3,000 won for 4 3 1 cubes is a lie. It's a
huge blessing that we were able to request 3 for the fat freezing table of the pasture grazing building. It's possible in our country. If you live in the US,
how much do you have to pay per kilogram? If you go
to the external meat selling sites and search for Class Pad
3, it's really very expensive. All the comments are
over 20,000 won. It can be viewed for more than 20,000 won. It's impossible to eat this in this dimension with blood.
Now, there's no other country than ours. Or, you can just
go to a local butcher shop that produces a lot of that kind of stuff and
send it to them with a knife or a small amount. Isn't it like that?
Ayako, you only paid 200,000 won, but
anyway, that's what I wanted to say earlier.
Yes,
Abe G,
he receives 3,000 won, but even if he receives 3,000 won, it's really not much.
4.
If you tailor the suit to Wikipedia, it'll be more even. On top of that, if you
add more fat, the packaging cost sometimes goes up. Since the
fat itself has almost no margin, I
hope you'll consider that and do something about it. Other people
[music]
asked me to send 4 of the Joint Chiefs of Staff quantitatively, but I
think it's a bit like that.
So, earlier, when you first announced the quantity, you asked me to
send it to a wholesaler with 2,000 won, and
when you said that, in fact, this
kid is steadily increasing the fat.  Como would have written the prayer without knowing what to do, and he
probably didn't know what other people would order, but the teacher said, "
Now, if you guys do it and write it, I think it would be right to organize these things a little bit.
So, the price has changed from
3,000 won to 1,000 won.
Since it's mutually beneficial, it's important for the family to set the price appropriately. In
fact, I wish we could add options, like adding seasoning. I do
n't think we can think about that yet. I'll
tell you later. I can press the button.
So, I want to talk about this briefly.
Anyway, even if the church copy fat is 3,000 won, it's really a pair. In
fact, that's right. I agreed to go to Audi and get a prescription. Yesterday, Park Mo-mong
declared 3 per kilogram of fat and touched it. It went through and it's 300 won for 100g. Does that
make sense? Oh, it's too much. I'm so grateful. Is it wrong to ask for it?
Oh, please tell me about that. I can't get back what I've thrown away.  When you ask for
some when catching something like a parrot, if you leave some liver, I won't have any. If
you talk like this, you should make good use of these things.
Within the scope of what I can do, it's like
going to the peak and asking for more fat, and
within the scope of what I can cause, I'll
try to collect a book of great advice in various ways. Pie, right?
[Music]
Peraum, sugar, salt. I think this much is enough.
Oh, I think it was this much. I want to put in just the exiting guy. I think I'll fill the need for three whole buildings like this.
Right?
Think about it all and don't have that.
Uh, you're doing it? Are you doing it? There aren't many people who are busy, but if you follow the chaos,
something like 2p 1 will come up, and you become a person.
In the article, there's an article about the detoxification method for pork. Please
read that.
In the case of pork, if you just grill it raw and
eat it raw, it's
not like eating raw meat, but it's blue. Even if you come and eat it, you
have to neutralize it because there is a country. Salt it.
There are methods like pickling or inserting a culvert, but I have to marinate it and do this.
Otherwise, it becomes a king and is a
burden on the body, so if you eat it as an object, you especially throw it away. At
the mart, you ride it and trim it, and you have to sell the remaining r internal organs and skins as if
you were walking. Ah,
the hair comes out and the
sound is just one more thing that I insisted on. Now, the first
four people, the book, are also sold separately. So, it would be good to use a server. The
initial
state, a,
everything that produces such a thing is included.
Yongseong, other, Min and Yeongseon, vitamins, so I dare say, Mr. and the.
I eat it raw, but sometimes it's good to cook it. I
wish I could sell it separately by putting it up in the store, but I'll have to
wait and see about that.
So, even if you take off as much as the customer, to be honest, where would you buy more?
This is actually from our perspective, but there
are only a few places. The options really can't be included. So, to be honest,
teacher, I'll do the flavor. Even if you do it like this, it's never that
great. Part 2 will go in, but there's no definitive method,
so even so, it's like this, 9,000 won.  3,000 won. If it's 3,000 won, I
'd like to make it possible today. I also
know the singer. Listen to what you say.
Fall, Gu, short ribs, etc. Team 1 loss. But, of course,
of course, in front, a large
5-pin water draining is almost impossible in our country. In the
old days, gays in our country did
n't eat distributed meat, so anywhere, people would say, "
Hey, that
kind of thing isn't well managed, and there are cases where it's not fresh, and
because of that, the condition can get bad. So, um, the
water was drained and things like that. This kind of payment gift is especially worse.
Now,
if it's not like that, it's
all sacred these days.
Choose a specific one.
What do you say? And it's better to lose a lot. When you remove the team,
all the minerals are drained
there. When you cook it here, all the robin's lare is drained. So,
don't throw away the 6th album and eat it together. It's good to
remove the basis.
It's not a state that runs further from the movie in advance.
Among the pork furniture.  Alarm once, pluster, like this cup, 5
flies, dull grinding, students, basically, salt or sugar points,
can this be better than eating the Bible in the form you wanted?
4 And then it can be better. Rather than just thinking about it, it
might be better to control it like that, even if it's seasoned.
If I'm not particularly allergic to the seasoned food or
if it contains something I really shouldn't eat, it's actually better to salt it
than to eat it raw, so it's
not difficult because you just have to drag the props.
But if I really have to eat raw meat or something like that, I do
n't think there's a way to come up with this kind of pre-seasoned step in the first place. It
was also mentioned in the academic section. If you
look at the Instagram feed of the Yang family,
there are many people who cut and grill the Yang family. They just cut the Yang family and grill it
first, and then sear the meat gut in the oil that comes out and
eat it.
Then, they grill it with other songs, sprinkle salt, and throw it away.
What do you think about the taste? It
seems like it's been a long time under the commercial district without any neck or fish intestines, but did you start with a pattern from the beginning?
In the real world, eating it gives you a lot of inside.
Here, are you talking about the liver seasoning? I've had
it for three years now, so I don't eat shark much, but I almost poured it
all over my body, so I don't really care. I'm
looking at the store here and the leader, isn't it a masterpiece? I
can't eat cooked liver well, and even if I force myself to eat it, I can't eat it well. I eat liver raw. Of course,
it might be better if you cook it, but I
think the baby ate too much raw salmon. He actually became softer, and
there's something like that, but I don't think there's a big difference. Now, in the case of the liver,
I do
n't have any opinions, and neither does that gentleman. I
couldn't eat this king girl anymore. I really should eat it raw,
especially the gamguk, etc. The texture and taste of the cooked liver were both
bad, so I thought about it and just thought about it. The law is to adjust the salt and
then add 10g of mysterious salt.
Onion, anyway, the intestines. I just
eat this again, and it's not like I'm going to cry out and be
precious, and there's no such thing, so I'll say more.
The texture is a bit unique, and since it has its own unique texture, it
might be rejected because it's not used to it. I understand, but
the taste itself is not like that. It's like cutting it with water and putting it in a co-pro. It's
half-baked, but I think it's a difference in perception. If you
cook it well, you absolutely hate it. I
think it's a drink that you can't drink. Hogan can be made into a show pro,
especially since people have been eating it since they were young.
So, I
'll finish with the question of Mr. Lee Sang-mon. Is
there a possibility of raw additives because you ate it in Anyang Dansaek? I ca
n't say there aren't any. So, before eating this raw, I usually freeze it for about two weeks and then
tell you what it means.
You just ate more, but
when I eat it and recommend it to others, I freeze it for about two weeks and
most parasites die, so you don't have to worry.
Western A Price cuts it and puts it in
ice and then eats it raw. When you want to eat it, you can
freeze it for about two weeks and then eat it. Other places also do it for about two weeks and then put it up for about two weeks and then
eat something else.
Oh, yes, cleansing,
that kind of thing.
Rather, I think that my thirst has diminished as time has passed since I had cancer. It
may vary from person to person, but
I actually really wanted to eat a lot, so I wrote about it and
stuff, but now both countries are
fine. The media doesn't really want to eat anything different. As I
mentioned last time, I think it would be good if you consider things like eating plenty of food at restaurants, Assel Pack, and
what you eat first thing in the morning this month, and if you
consider things like that important, it would be good from the beginning to the end. And even if I
cheat, it's different because I know that I'm setting it up and chatting,
so
when I eat this, I'm just eating the burnt fat, so I
think it's keto, and I eat it thinking that it's a lot of clothes. I'm
chatting about 5 foods and putting in false vegetable oils and whole
grains, and if you
know the price of alcohol, it's
a little more. Did
you write that? When I choose food, it's a more sweet standard. I'll
provide the basis, and even if I choose, I'll
make sure that I eat better when I eat snacks.
It's like a parka.
Oh, now that I think about it, that's it.  Just like today, I'm
going to try to
do something similar next time, like I talked about hair loss today, but what are you going to do next?
If you want to do something like that, you can DM me or something like that.
I'm thinking about what to do next.
Yes, I'm
planning to write once in a while because the color and texture are really pretty. I
think YouTube won't be easy either. I wrote it
first through my blog or Instagram.
RV. This is a lot of curd. Since I'm
doing it today, I
'll do something like this on Saturday about quitting smoking.
Anyway, I hope you finish your evening well. I
hope you guys hear more about the discussion. Oh, I'm glad it
didn't work out. I
'll see you again next Saturday. Bye.
4. Finishing. Asco. I
hope you spend it okay.